Negar Eghbali



Junior Frontend Developer

Location: Brøndbytoften, 2605 Brøndby

Mobile: +4591973545 **E-Mail:** negar.en@gmail.com

LinkedIn: http://www.linkedin.com/in/negaren

Github: https://github.com/negaren **Citizenship:** Iran, Danish work permit

Summary

Besides the project management experience I had in the IT and e-commerce industry, I dived in learning web-development with Hack Your Future (CPH). I have delivered projects using HTML, CSS, Java script, MYSQL, React, Nodejs and some other technologies aside and currently working as a part of a team on developing a webshop.

General Skills

- Web development
- E-commerce
- Cross-cultural communication
- CRM
- Project management
- Account management

Work Experience

Project Manager | Karinaco | 2016-2020

Business nature: An e-commerce project with the aim of supplying and distributing products only through online platforms.

Responsibilities:

- Managing the development team and helping them Identify customer needs, challenges, and wishes
- Liaising communication among project stakeholders
- Help development team to have a user-centered product vision
- Delivering business analytic reports to help online distributor venture run its business in the market

Result: The desired platforms were delivered on the scheduled time, and the team was trained to maintain and update content on a regular basis.

Key Account Manager | Rocket Internet (Bamilo) | 2015-2016

Business nature: A marketplace platform that was representing product of various categories that were supplied by clients, and representing online shops to clients.

Responsibilities:

- Managing more than 35 tier1 accounts of the E-commerce business and helping suppliers to hit their online sale targets
- Providing weekly, monthly KPI reports analyzing the achievement of sales, product display, successful clicks, and digital marketing parameters
- Analyzing digital marketing and user experience reports and running planned campaigns
- Managing meetings with suppliers and facilitating communication among them and other respective teams
- Planning to develop the business by focusing on growing clients
- Increasing seller's performance to 30% more than initiation in 3 months

Result: Improving more than 15 tier 3 accounts to tier 1 place in less than three months, helping clients to improve sales numbers by strategic planning.

Project Manager | Rocket Internet (Snappfood) | 2014-2015

Business nature: Food marketplace start-up.

Responsibilities:

- Team building and managing members to deliver tasks and facilitating communication among stakeholders
- Training and coaching team members
- Holding regular basis meetings with the technical team to increase user experience quality
- Optimizing cross-functional teams collaboration
- Scheduling and planning operational and sale team targets
- Launched the project on planned time and was invited to join the holding seminar as best performed team among middle east countries ventures

Result: Launching the project in less than 3 months, the team of customer service, content managers, graphic designers were trained to establish the required processes on a regular basis and, myteam and I achieved the title of the first launched project among middle east countries' ventures of Rocket Internet holding.

Projects

- Online webshop (ongoing)
- Meal sharing
- weather Application
- Github search
- Gifv search
- Faster presser

Education

- Web Development | Hack Your Future Denmark (Copenhagen) | September 2021 Ongoing
- MBA (Master of Business Administration) General Management| Farhang Matin higher Education institute | 2012 2014
- BSc Computer Science (software) | Azad University | 2005 2009

Technical Skills

IT Skills:

- **HTML**, beginner
- **CSS**, beginner
- Java Script, beginner
- **git,** beginner
- Nodejs, beginner
- Mysql, beginner
- React, beginner
- Agile, Scrum, familiar with

Soft Skills

- Service minded
- Result oriented
- People management
- Recruitment
- Account management
- Sales and marketing

Languages

- Danish | Beginner
- English | Fluent
- Turkish | Fluent
- Persian | Native

Reference

Mikkel Bendixsen, Head of event at TechBBQ

Email: mbe@techbbq.org

Mobile: 29245607